Eric Libardi Pereira

+351 91 292 0287



eric_pereira04@hotmail.com



Lisbon, Portugal



linkedin.com/in/ericlibardi



github.com/ericlibardi



ericlibardi.com

Technical Skills

Angular .NET

|avaScript C#

Typescript Node.JS*

HTML5 MySQL

CSS3 MongoDB*

SCRUM

SASS AJAX

, y, o

Bootstrap Git

Tailwind

jQuery

lonic

React.|S*

(*) Foundations

Soft Skills

- Analytical and problem solving
- Fast learner
- Team player
- Well organized
- Proactive

Languages

Portuguese – Native English – Full Professional Full-Stack developer who is passionate for coding and technologies. Fascinated for a well-written code, because it is not all about working, but also working perfectly. With a diverse experience and an exemplar dedication while studying, I will bring my best to the game.

Nationality: an EU citizen based in Portugal.

Education

<Academia de Código> - Lisbon, Portugal 2022-05 / 2022-08

A 14 week Intensive && Immersive Fullstack Programming Bootcamp

Ubiqum Code Academy – Lisbon, Portugal 2020-01 / 2020-06

Coding Bootcamp, Full Stack Web Developer

ISEG – Lisbon, Portugal 2018-08 / 2019-06

Post graduation, Prospection and Strategy

ESPM – São Paulo, Brazil 2013-08 / 2015-06

Post graduation in Business Management

ESPM – São Paulo, Brazil 2009-01 / 2012-12

Bachelor's Degree in Marketing

Experience

Full-Stack Developer

WeAreFabrica - Lisbon, Portugal

2023-10 - current

- Develop and maintain user-friendly web applications/ interfaces
- Contribute to front-end and back-end development processes
- Build new product features and components
- Build APIs on the server side
- Perform tests, troubleshoot software, and fix bugs
- Collaborate with other departments on projects and sprints

 $\underline{\sf Skills:} \ \, \mathsf{Angular} \cdot \mathsf{TypeScript} / \ \, \mathsf{Javascript} \cdot \mathsf{SASS} \cdot . \mathsf{NET} \cdot \mathsf{Tailwind} \cdot \mathsf{REST} \, \, \mathsf{APIs} \cdot \mathsf{RxJS} \cdot \\ \mathsf{HTML5} \cdot \mathsf{CSS}$

FrontEnd Developer

Whale - Lisbon, Portugal

2022-08 - 2023-09

- Developing and implementing user-friendly web applications.
- Collaborating with back-end developers, UX designers, and other stakeholders to ensure seamless integration of front-end and back-end functionalities.
- Writing clean, efficient, and well-documented code that adheres to best practices and coding standards.
- Continuously improving the performance, reliability, and security of web applications.

 $\underline{\mathsf{Skills:}} \ \mathsf{TypeScript} \cdot \mathsf{Angular} \cdot \mathsf{SASS} \cdot \mathsf{Syncfusion} \cdot \mathsf{REST} \ \mathsf{APIs} \cdot \mathsf{RxJS} \cdot \mathsf{JavaScript} \cdot \\ \mathsf{HTML5} \cdot \mathsf{CSS}$

Projects

Web Application - Food Delivery

Web application where users can request Food to have it delivered to their company. Assisting on the development of the front-end application and the backend APIs of the server. Developed in Angular, Typescript/ Javascript, .NET, Tailwind, Html, CSS/SASS

Web Application – Company Management

Web application to help transportation companies manage their routine. Responsible for developing the Front-End of the project. Developed in Angular, Typescript, Html, CSS3/SASS, Syncfusion

Whatsapp Bot

Bot to automatically respond users according to the message sent. Developed during a Hackaton challenge, being selected as the winner project. Javascript, Node.JS, HTML, CSS

Dungeon - Game

Game similar to Dungeon and Dragons in style, developed during the Bootcamp. Developed in Java, Simple GFX Library, Git, Apache Ant

My Tasks

Webapp for daily tasks management. Developed as a personal project for portfolio. Made with HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Redux, Git.

My Itinerary

Responsive webapp for touristic itineraries, where users can search for itineraries for searched city. Personal project for portfolio. Made with React.JS/Redux, MongoDB, Node.js, Javascript, HTML5. CSS3, Bootstrap

Courses

Angular, Udemy Complete course

CS50 – Harvard Principles of programming

Typescript, Udemy Basics of typescript

Javascript Guide, Udemy Complete course

Digital Marketing – Illinois University